Mss.Ms.Coll.113
American Philosophical Society
- Series VII. Committees and Organizations, 10.5 linear feet
  - Study of Satellite Power Systems - Correspondence, 1979; 2.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Environmental Studies Board. (Box 37)
  - Correspondence with Dr. Friedman, 1980-1981; 18.0 items; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Geophysics Film Committee. (Box 37)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, 1975-1976; 19.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, Folder 1, 1977; 41.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, Folder 2, 1977; 40.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, Folder 1, 1978; 58.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, Folder 2, 1978; 28.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, Folder 3, 1978; 17.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, 1979-1981; 27.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 39)
  - Data Interchange and Data Centers, 1976-1977; 11.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 39)
  - Data Interchange and Data Centers, 1978; 17.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 38)
  - Membership Profiles, 1977-1979; 4.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 39)
  - Solar-Terrestrial Research Committee, Correspondence and Reports, 1976-1981; 23.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Geophysics Research Board. (Box 39)
  - Benjamin Apthorp Gould Fund - Nomination and Recommendation Letters, 1969-1978; undated; 50.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 39)
  - Reports and Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1969-1971; 25.0 items; Jicamarca Radar Observatory.; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 39)
  - Meeting of the Council - Agenda and Preliminary Reports - Folder 1, 1979 June; 50.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 39)
  - Meeting of the Council - Memoranda and Reports - Folder 2, 1979 August; 40.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Meeting of the Council - Memoranda and Reports - Folder 3, 1979 August; 50.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Meeting of the Council - Agenda, Ballot Results, Reports, 1979 October 28; 75.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Nomination Forms, 1989; 18.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Nomination Forms, 1991-1992; 15.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Office of Internal Audit, Annual Report, 1993; 1.0 item; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.)
  - Office of Internal Audit, Fourth Quarter Audit Plan, 1993; 1.0 item; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Public Welfare Medal - Nominations and Recommendation Letters, 1993; 4.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Report Review Committee - Correspondence and Reports to Dr. Friedman, 1974-1977; 11.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Report to the Auditing Committee, Nature and Scope of Services to be Provide for the Financial Year Ending June 30, 1993, 1.0 item; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 40)
  - Review of the US/USSR Agreement on Cooperation in the Fields of Science and Technology, 1977 May; 1.0 item; National Research Council (U.S.). Commission on International Relations. (Box 40)
    This single item spans 176 pages.
  - Task Group on Astronomy and Astrophysics, Major Directions for Space Sciences: 1995-2015, 1986; 1.0 item; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 41)
    This single item totals 111 pages.
  - Task Group on Fundamental Physics and Chemistry, Major Directions for Space Sciences 1995-2015 and Other Executive Summaries, 1985 February 1; 1986 March; 1986 April 2; 4.0 items; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 41)
  - Letters and Reports to Herbert Friedman, 1978; 1980; 11.0 items; U.S. National Committee for the International Union of Geodesy and Geophysics. (Box 41)
  - Trip Report of a Visit to the USSR by a Delegation of Members of the Nationa Academy of Sciences of the USA, June 19 - July 3, 1973, 1973 August 9; 9.0 items; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Office of the Foreign Secretary. (Box 41)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, 1967-1971; 15.0 items; United States. Astronomy Missions Board. (Box 41)
  - NASA, Office of Grants and Research Contracts. George R. Carruthers Proposals, 1966-1968; 42.0 items; United States. Office of Space Science and Applications. (Box 41)
  - NASA, Office of Grants and Research Contracts. George R. Carruthers Proposals., 1962; 1972; 21.0 items; United States. Office of Space Science and Applications. (Box 41)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, 1973-1981; 55.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 42)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, 1958-1972; 70.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 42)
  - Correspondence Regarding Nomination for NASA Chief Scientist, 1974-1975; 5.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. Office of Administration. (Box 42)
    From 1974-1975, Dr. Friedman served on an Informal Ad Hoc Subcommittee of the Physical Sciences Committee, in order to recommend candidates for the position of NASA Chief Scientist. This Subcommittee was abolished in June of 1975.
  - NASA Shuttle Payload Operations Conference, Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1977 October; 11.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. Shuttle Payloads Engineering Division. (Box 42)
  - NASA Shuttle Payload Operations Conference, Reports, 1977 October; 6.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. Shuttle Payloads Engineering Division. (Box 42)
  - Space Program Advisory Council, Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1974; 18.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 42)
  - Space Program Advisory Council, Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, Folder 1, 1975; 14.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 42)
  - Space Program Advisory Council, Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, Folder 2, 1975; 21.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 42)
  - Space Program Advisory Council, Correspondence with Friedman., 1976; 30.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 43)
  - Space Program Advisory Council, Committee Meetings and Minutes, 1976; 17.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 43, Box 42)
  - Space Program Advisory Council, Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1977-1978; 40.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 43)
  - Research Advisory Committee, Agendas and Staff Activities, 1990; 4.0 items; National Air and Space Museum. (Box 43)
  - Research Advisory Committee, Correspondence, Reports, and Findings, 1990-1991; 11.0 items; National Air and Space Museum. (Box 43)
  - Research Advisory Committee, Final Report, 1990; 2.0 items; National Air and Space Museum. (Box 43)
  - Research Advisory Committee, Report Draft, 1992; 1.0 item; National Air and Space Museum. (Box 43)
  - Advisory Board to the Office of Physical Sciences, Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1976-1980; 11.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 43)
  - Atmospheric Research Review Workshop Documents, 1978; 17.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 43)
  - Carbon Dioxide and Climate Report, 1979-1980; 14.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 43)
  - Climate Research Board Meeting - Materials, 1979 October 18-19; 40.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 44)
  - Climate Research Board - Agenda and Minutes, 1980 Decebmer 4-5; 14.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 43, Box 44)
  - Climate Research Board - Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1977; 4.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 44)
  - Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1980-1981; 8.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 44)
  - Joint Meeting of the Climate Research Board and a Proposal for a World Climate Program, 1979; 40.0 items; Assembly of Mathematical and Physical Sciences (U.S.). (Box 44)
  - Report - The Management, Organization, and Structure of the U.S. Climate Program, 1978; 1.0 item; National Research Council (U.S.). Climate Board. (Box 44)
  - Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, Climate Research Board, Board Member, 1979; 25.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Climate Board. (Box 44)
  - Interim Report and Proposal for the Continuation of Study of Postdoctorals in Science and Engineering in the United States, Folder 1, 1977-1978; 12.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Committee on a Study of Postdoctoral and Doctoral Research Staff in Science and Engineering. (Box 44)
  - Interim Report - Summary of Findings and Recommendations, 1978-1980; 1980 June 11; 12.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Committee on a Study of Postdoctoral and Doctoral Research Staff in Science and Engineering. (Box 45)
  - Report - Nonfacultuy Doctoral Research Staff in Science and Engineering in U.S. Universities; Related Correspondence, 1978-1979; 7.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Committee on a Study of Postdoctoral and Doctoral Research Staff in Science and Engineering. (Box 45)
  - Correspondence from Miscellaneous NRC Committees and Commissions, 1962-1986; 11.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.) (Box 45)
  - Letters to Herbert Friedman, 1988; 6.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications. (Box 45)
  - Criswell/Waldron Lunar Power System, Workshop Proceedings, Proposal, and Correspondence, 1991; 8.0 items; Criswell, David R.; Netrologic, Inc.. (Box 45)
  - Correspondence Regarding NSF Proposal - Solar Neutrons, 1977-1980; 8.0 items; National Science Foundation (U.S.). Division of Atmospheric Sciences. (Box 45)
  - Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1990 August; undated; 3.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Commission on Geosciences, Environment, and Resources. (Box 45)
  - Biographical Sketches of Board Members, 1975; 2.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Naval Studies Board. (Box 45)
  - Solar Power Satellite System Workshop, 1979; 19.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Environmental Studies Board. (Box 46)
  - Solar Terrestrial Research in the 1980s - Correspondence and Program Report, 1979-1980; 25.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.) (Box 46)
  - Correspondence to Herbert Friedman, 1980-1981; 3.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 46)
  - Committee Minutes and Correspondence to Herbert Friedman, 1972-1980; 21.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Committee on Space Astronomy and Astrophysics. (Box 46)
  - Institutional Arrangements for the Space Telescope, Report of a Study at Woods Hole, Massachussetts, 1976 July 19-30; 1.0 item; National Research Council (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 46)
  - International Aspects of Space Observatories, Conferenct at Williamsburg, VA, 1976 January 26-29; 11.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 46)
  - International Aspects of Space Observatories - Correspondence About Conference, 1975-1976; 3.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 46)
  - International Aspects of Space Observatories - Reports, 1976; 3.0 items; National Research Council (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 46)
  - Federal Government Official Form for Herbert Friedman, 1975 April 29; 1.0 item; National Science Foundation (U.S.). (Box 46)
  - Correspondence to and from Herbert Friedman, 1975-1976; 12.0 items; National Science Foundation (U.S.). Ad Hoc Advisory Group on Science Programs. (Box 46)
  - Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1978-1980; 9.0 items; National Science Foundation (U.S.) Division of Astronomical Sciences. (Box 46)
  - Correspondence to Herbert Friedman, 1973; 5.0 items; United States-Israel Binational Science Foundation. (Box 46)
  - Correspondence with North American Aviation, Inc., 1961-1963; 21.0 items; North American Aviation. (Box 46)
  - Correspondence to Herbert Friedman and Conference Materials, 1991; 6.0 items; NATO Advanced Study Institute. (Box 46)
  - Correspondence to Herbert Friedman, 1958-1965; 19.0 items; Philosophical Society of Washington (Washington, D.C.). (Box 46)
  - Correspondence to and from Herbert Friedman, 1961-1973; 20.0 items; United States. President’s Science Advisory Committee. (Box 46)
  - Advisory Council - Correspondence to Herbert Friedman, 1967-1976; 11.0 items; Princeton University. Dept. of Geological and Geophysical Sciences. (Box 46)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Friedman, 1973-1979; 73.0 items; Royal Society (Great Britain). Provisional Space Science Advisory Board for Europe. (Box 47)
  - Correspondence to Herbert Friedman, 1959-1974; 10.0 items; Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society of North America. (Box 47)
  - Naval Research Lab-RESA Science Awards Board, 1956-1958; 4.0 items; Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society of North America. (Box 47)
  - Correspondence to and from Herbert Friedman, 13.0 items; United States. Navy. Senior Executive Service Management System. (Box 47)
  - Materials Regarding Skylab/Apollo Telescope Mount, 1978-1979; 10.0 items; Skylab Program. (Box 47)
  - Space Science - Past and Prologue, 1976; 14.0 items; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 47)
    "Space Science - Past and Prologue" was a symposium organized by the Naval Research Laboratory in honor of Dr. Friedman. This folder contains some correspondence relating to the symposium. The symposium was held on May 24, 1976, at the National Academy of Sciences in Washingon, D.C.
  - Space Science - Past and Prologue - Friedman's Remarks and Symposium Program, 1976; undated; 8.0 items; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 47)
  - Editorial Board Correspondence, including Herbert Friedman, 1961-1976; 28.0 items; Space Science Reviews. (Box 47)
  - A Strategy for the Detection and Study of Extrasolar Planetary Material, 1990-2000, 1989 June; 1.0 item; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 47)
  - Development of Instruments for Planetary Exploration Spacecraft, A Report, 1989 June; 1.0 item; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Space Science Board. (Box 47)
  - Princeton Advisory Committee on Space Telescope Science Institute - Correspondence, 1976-1979; 20.0 items; Space Telescope Science Institute (U.S.). (Box 47)
  - Minutes and Correspondence with Herbert Friedman, 1976; 68.0 items; Universities Research Association (U.S.). (Box 48)
  - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, and Reports, 1977-1978; 36.0 items; Universities Space Research Association. (Box 48)
  - Appointment of Herbert Friedman to Visiting Committee to the Division of Physical Sciences, 1974-1978; 14.0 items; University of Chicago. Division of the Physical Sciences. (Box 48)
  - Correspondence to and from Herbert Friedman, 1960-1972; 13.0 items; University of Maryland at College Park. (Box 48)
  - Correspondence to and from Herbert Friedman, 1974-1977; 10.0 items; University of Pennsylvania. (Box 48)
  - Award to Herbert Friedman, Nominations of Other Scientists, 1989-1991; 10.0 items; Wolf Foundation Prizes. (Box 48)
  - Correspondence and Meeting Materials, 1990-1992; 14.0 items; World Space Congress (1992: Washington, D.C.). (Box 48)
  - Appointment as Visiting Professor, 1966-1968; 17.0 items; Yale University. (Box 48)
- Series VIII. Certificates and Awards, 0.5 linear feet
  Series VIII contains the many certificates and awards bestowed to Dr. Friedman during his lifetime, as well as related correspondence and announcements. Among Dr. Friedman’s awards that the series contains are the Eddington Medal of the Royal Astronomical Society, the National Medal of Science, the Henry Norris Russell Lectureship of the American Astronomical Society, the William Bowie Medal of the American Geophysical Union, and the Wolf Foundation Prize in Physics. Some material has been removed to oversize.
  - International Cooperation Award Presented to Herbert Friedman, 1991 May 2; 1.0 item; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 56)
  - Dryden Research Lecture Given By Herbert Friedman, 1973; 1.0 item; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 56)
  - Herbert Friedman Elected to the Grade of Honorary Fellow, 1993 May 5; 1.0 item; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 56)
  - National Medal of Science Awarded to Herbert Friedman, 1968; 1.0 item; United States. President. (Box 56)
  - Certificate of Appointment as Member of the Advisory Committee for the Directorate of Physical Sciences, 1962 July 1; 1.0 item; United States. Air Force. Office of Scientific Research. (Box 49)
  - Fellowship Certificate, 1963 January 3; 1.0 item; American Association for the Advancement of Science. (Box 49)
  - Fifty Year Member Certificate, 2000 June; 2.0 items; American Astronomical Society. (Box 49)
  - W. Randolph Lovelace, II Award, 1973 June 20; 1.0 item; American Astronautical Society. (Box 49)
  - Nomination of Herbert Friedman to the Astronautics Award, 1964 May; 2.0 items; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 49)
  - Dryden Award to Herbert Friedman, Press Release, 1973 January 9; 1.0 item; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 49)
  - International Cooperation Award, 1991; 4.0 items; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 49)
  - Nomination of Herbert Friedman as Honorary Fellow, 1992 June; 4.0 items; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 49)
  - Space Science Award to Herbert Friedman, 1963 December 14; 5.0 items; American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics. (Box 49)
  - Nomination of Herbert Friedman for Arctowski Medal, 1986 July; 2.0 items; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) (Box 49)
  - Solicitation for Nominations, for the Prix Balzan 1989, 2.0 items; International Balzan Foundation. (Box 49)
  - Bower Award and Prize for Achievement in Science, 1993 June-August; 3.0 items; Franklin Institute (Philadelphia, Pa.). (Box 49)
  - Captain Robert Dexter Conrad Award to Herbert Friedman and Nomination Materials, 1961 May; 10.0 items; United States. Navy. (Box 49)
  - Thirty-Third Cosmos Club Award to Herbert Friedman, Congratulatory Letters, 1996; 36.0 items; Cosmos Club (Washington, D.C.). (Box 49)
  - Distinguished Civilian Service Award, Citation for Herbert Friedman, undated; 1.0 item; United States. Dept. of Defense.; United States. Distinguished Civilian Service Awards Board. (Box 49)
  - Recognition of Achievement, Senior Executive - Herbert Friedman, 1974 March; 1.0 item; United States. Navy. (Box 49)
  - Eddington Medal - Press Release and Correspondence, 1964 January-June; 4.0 items; Royal Astronomical Society.. (Box 49)
  - Michelson Award to Herbert Friedman - Congratulatory Letters and Award Report, 1972; 6.0 items; Franklin Institute (Philadelphia, Pa.). (Box 49)
  - Janssen Medal Awarded to Herbert Friedman - Correspondence, 1962; 4.0 items; Societe francaise de photographie. (Box 49)
  - Janssen Prize - Correspondence, 1990 May 7; 2.0 items; Societe astronomique de France. (Box 49)
  - Massey Medal Awarded to Herbert Friedman, 1992 June; 11.0 items; Royal Society (Great Britain). (Box 49)
  - Programs from Award Ceremonies and Press Releases, 1957-1980; 11.0 items (Box 49)
  - Other Awards Given to Herbert Friedman, 1951-1964; 4.0 items (Box 49)
    This folder includes awards from the American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, American Rocket Society, the American Academy fo Arts and Sciences, and the Royal Order of Radiated Desert Rats.
  - Herbert Friedman's Delegate Certificate to the Thirteenth General Assembly of the International Radio Scientifc Union in London, 1960 August 1; 1.0 item; National Research Council (U.S.) (Box 49)
  - Apollo Achievement Award to Herbert Friedman, 1969 July 20; 1.0 item; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 49)
  - NASA Group Achievement Award for the Apollo Soyuz Test Project Experiments Team, 1975 September 16; 2.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 49)
  - Exceptional Scientific Achievement Medal, undated; 2.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. (Box 57)
  - Exceptional Scientific Achievement Medal, undated; 2.0 items; United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 57)
  - Presentation of the National Medal of Science to Herbert Friedman, 1969 January 17; 18.0 items; United States. President's Committee on the National Medal of Science. (Box 49)
    This folder contains programs and stationary from the award ceremony event at the White House.
  - National Medal of Science - Congratulatory Letters to Herbert Friedman, 1969; 40.0 items; United States. President's Committee on the National Medal of Science. (Box 49)
  - Navy Award for Distinguished Ahievement in Science - Press Release and Letter, 1962; 3.0 items; United States. Navy. (Box 49)
  - NRL Lifetime Achievement Award and Symposium for Dr. Herbert Friedman, 1996; 33.0 items; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 49)
  - Space Science - Past and Prologue, Symposium in Honor of Herbert Friedman, Programs and Correspondence, 1976 May; 11.0 items; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 49)
  - 75th Anniversary Award for Innovation Presented to Herbert Friedman - First Detection of X Rays from the Sun, 1998 June 19; 1.0; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 55)
  - 75th Anniversary Award for Innovation Presented to Herbert Friedman - Quantitative X-Ray Fluorescence Analysis, 1998 June 19; 1.0 item; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 55)
  - 75th Anniversary Award for Innovation Presented to Herbert Friedman - X-Ray Astronomy, 1998 June 19; 1.0 item; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 55)
  - 75th Anniversary Award for Innovation Presented to Herbert Friedman - SOLRAD I, 1998 June 19; 1.0 item; Naval Research Laboratory (U.S.). (Box 55)
  - Nomination of Herbert Friedman for Nobel Prize for Physics 1985, 1984-1986; 9.0 items; Nobel Prizes. (Box 49)
  - Fellowship Certificate Awarded to Herbert Friedman, 2.0 items; Optical Society of America. (Box 49)
  - President's Award for Distinguished Federal Civilan Service, 1964; 9.0 items; United States. President. (Box 49)
  - President's Award for Distinguished Federal Civilian Service, Correspondence, 1964; 5.0 items; United States. President. (Box 49)
  - Rockefeller Public Service Award to Herbert Friedman, Programs and Correspondence, 1967 December; 6.0 items; Princeton University. (Box 49)
  - Rockefeller Public Service Award to Herbert Friedman, Programs and Newspaper Clippings, 1967; 47.0 item.; Princeton University. (Box 49)
  - Russell Lectureship Awarded to Herbert Friedman, 2.0 items; American Astronomical Society. (Box 49)
  - Career Service Award for Fifty Years of Service., 1993 September 1; 1.0 item; United States. Navy. (Box 49)
  - Award for Distinguished Achievement in Science, 1962 October; 2.0 items; United States. Navy. (Box 49)